question_data = [
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Greenland is almost as big as Africa.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Greenland is covered with grass and Iceland covered with ice.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The Republic of Malta is the smallest microstate worldwide.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Alaska is the largest state in the United States.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "There are no deserts in Europe.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "California is larger than Japan.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Tokyo is the capital of Japan.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Hungary is the only country in the world beginning with H.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "New Haven is the capital city of the state of Connecticut in the United States.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Rhode Island is actually located on the US mainland, despite its name.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
